A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1971-1980 FA401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1972
  - International, 1972/100
    - McKelvey, John J., Jr. (Reel 2, Frame 335)
    - Morris, O. Frank (Reel 2, Frame 364)
    - Nickel, John L. (Reel 2, Frame 390)
    - Niederhauser, John S. (Reel 2, Frame 427)
    - Owens, Patrick N. (Reel 2, Frame 479)
    - Parson, William (Reel 2, Frame 501)
    - Pino, John A. (Reel 2, Frame 611)
    - Pomeroy, Charles R. (Reel 2, Frame 648)
    - Renfro, Bobby L. (Reel 2, Frame 672)
    - Sanders, Alvin J. (Research) (Reel 2, Frame 713)
    - Shope, Robert E. (Reel 2, Frame 735)
    - Smeltzer, Dale G. (Reel 2, Frame 837)
    - Soto, Pablo E. (Reel 2, Frame 877)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Holland, Robert C.) (Reel 2, Frame 942)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Sawyer, William D.) (Reel 2, Frame 1020)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Sturrock, Robert F.) (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (C-W) (Reel 3, Frame 184)
    - Stewart, Michael M. (Reel 3, Frame 286)
    - Sturrock, Robert F. (Reel 3, Frame 324)
    - Traywick, Jack Dee (Reel 3, Frame 363)
    - Wellhausen, Edwin J. (Reel 3, Frame 402)
    - Wortman, L. Sterling (Travel) (Reel 3, Frame 470)
    - Wray, Joe D. (Reel 3, Frame 578)
    - A-E (Reel 3, Frame 626)
    - F-H (Reel 3, Frame 759)
    - I-L (Reel 3, Frame 1032)
    - M-P (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - R-T (Reel 4, Frame 129)
    - U-Y (Reel 4, Frame 320)
  - Applications for Employment, 1972/101
    - A-S (Reel 4, Frame 535)
  - International Organizations, 1972/103
    - Diplomatic Services (B-V) (Reel 4, Frame 550)
    - International Bank (A-M) (Reel 4, Frame 574)
    - International Bank (N-W) (Reel 4, Frame 718)
    - International Council for Educational Development (C-P) (Reel 4, Frame 883)
    - International Federation of Gynecology and Obstetrics (Reel 4, Frame 988)
    - International Study Centers Directors (Conferences) (Reel 4, Frame 1083)
    - International (A-C) (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - International (E-W) (Reel 5, Frame 207)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (A-U) (Reel 5, Frame 390)
    - United Nations (Human Environment Conference) (Reel 5, Frame 585)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (B-P) (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - United Nations (A-S) (Reel 6, Frame 197)
    - United Nations Development Programme (E-S) (Reel 6, Frame 282)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (C-O) (Reel 6, Frame 583)
    - United Nations Research Institute for Social Development (Apthorpe, Raymond) (Reel 6, Frame 611)
    - United Nations University (Reel 6, Frame 618)
    - A-N (Reel 6, Frame 665)
    - P-W (Reel 6, Frame 869)
    - International Organizations - Virus Studies, 1972/103.V
      - United Nations (World Health Organization) (Reel 6, Frame 1058)
  - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), 1972/116
    - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (Reel 6, Frame 1060)
  - United States, 1972/200
    - Agribusiness Council, Inc. (Camp, W. B.) (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Ab-Ag (Reel 7, Frame 243)
    - American Council on Education (A-O) (Reel 7, Frame 358)
    - American Council on Education, Overseas Liaison Committee (Supplementary Material) (Reel 7, Frame 394)
    - American Freedom from Hunger Foundation, Inc. (Reel 7, Frame 552)
    - American (A-F) (Reel 7, Frame 634)
    - American (G-P) (Reel 7, Frame 842)
    - American Theater (Reel 7, Frame 928)
    - American (S-U) (Reel 7, Frame 991)
    - Al-Am (Reel 7, Frame 1081)
    - An (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Ar-Au (Reel 8, Frame 116)
    - B-Ba (Reel 8, Frame 412)
    - Be (Reel 8, Frame 698)
    - Boston (I-U) (Reel 8, Frame 833)
    - Bi-Bo (Reel 8, Frame 903)
    - Br (Reel 8, Frame 1059)
    - Bu (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Ca (Reel 9, Frame 140)
    - Center (A-C) (Reel 9, Frame 405)
    - Center (N-W) (Reel 9, Frame 602)
    - Chesapeake Bay Research Consortium (Reel 9, Frame 780)
    - Christian Action Ministry (Health Care) (Reel 9, Frame 908)
    - Clark Foundation (Hoffman, Donald B.) (Reel 9, Frame 981)
    - Ce-Cl (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Columbia College, Chicago (Theatre Arts) (Reel 10, Frame 355)
    - Columbia University (A-W) (Reel 10, Frame 408)
    - Coc-Col (Reel 10, Frame 527)
    - Community (B-S) (Reel 10, Frame 620)
    - Com (Reel 10, Frame 709)
    - Con (Reel 10, Frame 845)
    - Cornell University (A-M) (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Cornell University (N-W) (Reel 11, Frame 193)
    - Coo-Cou (Reel 11, Frame 390)
    - Cr-Cu (Reel 11, Frame 570)
    - Danforth Foundation (C-S) (Reel 11, Frame 583)
    - Da (Reel 11, Frame 793)
    - De-Du (Reel 11, Frame 955)
    - Educational (C-P) (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Energy Policy Project (Reel 12, Frame 93)
    - Experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. (Reel 12, Frame 95)
    - E (Reel 12, Frame 333)
    - Federation of Southern Cooperatives (Reel 12, Frame 699)
    - F-Fl (Reel 12, Frame 796)
    - Ford Foundation (A-W) (Reel 12, Frame 899)
    - Foundation Executives Group (Reel 12, Frame 1073)
    - Fo (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Fr-Fu (Reel 13, Frame 152)
    - George Washington University (E-W) (Reel 13, Frame 238)
    - G-Ge (Reel 13, Frame 408)
    - Gi-Gu (Reel 13, Frame 540)
    - Harvard University (Medical and Demographic History) (Reel 13, Frame 754)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health (P-S) (Reel 13, Frame 1120)
    - Harvard University (B-W) (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Hawaiian Sugar Planters' Association (C-S) (Reel 14, Frame 243)
    - H-Ha (Reel 14, Frame 497)
    - Howard University (A-E) (Reel 14, Frame 689)
    - He-Ho (Reel 14, Frame 766)
    - Hu-Hy (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Institute (A-T) (Reel 15, Frame 250)
    - International Center, Hawaii (C-P) (Reel 15, Frame 456)
    - International Development Foundation, Inc. (Sloane, Ann B.) (Reel 15, Frame 655)
    - International (B-P) (Reel 15, Frame 734)
    - Iowa State University (E-S) (Reel 15, Frame 803)
    - I (Reel 15, Frame 1055)
    - Johns Hopkins University (Population Dynamics) (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Johns Hopkins University (H-W) (Reel 16, Frame 77)
    - J (Reel 16, Frame 209)
    - Kansas State University (Beck, Glenn H.) (Reel 16, Frame 508)
    - K (Reel 16, Frame 520)
    - La-Li (Reel 16, Frame 754)
    - Los Angeles Technical Services Corporation (Reel 16, Frame 916)
    - Lo-Lu (Reel 16, Frame 948)
    - Macy Foundation (D-T) (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (D-T) (Reel 17, Frame 140)
    - Ma (Reel 17, Frame 267)
    - Mc (Reel 17, Frame 485)
    - Me (Reel 17, Frame 620)
    - Michigan State University (Wittwer, Sylvan H.) (Reel 17, Frame 831)
    - Michigan State University (E-W) (Reel 17, Frame 930)
    - Mi (Reel 17, Frame 1085)
    - Mo-My (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - National Academy of Sciences (A-Z) (Reel 18, Frame 99)
    - National (A) (Reel 18, Frame 499)
    - National (B-H) (Reel 18, Frame 627)
    - National Research Council (D-Y) (Reel 18, Frame 862)
    - National (I-R) (Reel 18, Frame 889)
    - National (S-U) (Reel 18, Frame 1058)
    - New York (C-M) (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - New York Public Library (A-W) (Reel 19, Frame 359)
    - New York University (E-N) (Reel 19, Frame 398)
    - New York University, Environmental Medicine (Supplementary Material) (Reel 19, Frame 450)
    - New York (P-U) (Reel 19, Frame 457)
    - New (C-Y) (Reel 19, Frame 584)
    - Na-Ne (Reel 19, Frame 694)
    - Ni (Reel 19, Frame 879)
    - No-Nu (Reel 19, Frame 970)
    - O-Oh (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Ok-Ow (Reel 20, Frame 181)
    - Peace Corps (Colombian Health Care) (Reel 20, Frame 294)
    - Pa-Pe (Reel 20, Frame 479)
    - Pf-Pl (Reel 20, Frame 692)
    - Population Council, Inc. (A-S) (Reel 20, Frame 844)
    - Princeton University (A-F) (Reel 20, Frame 942)
    - Princeton University (G-J) (Reel 20, Frame 1025)
    - Princeton University (L-Y) (Reel 20, Frame 1120)
    - Purdue University (A-T) (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Purdue University, Small-Farm Workshop (Supplementary Material) (Reel 21, Frame 199)
    - Purdue University, Social Change and Pollution Control (Supplementary Material) (Reel 21, Frame 814)
    - Po-Pu (Reel 21, Frame 992)
    - Queens College, North Carolina (Smylie, John E.) (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - Quinault Indian Tribe (Reel 22, Frame 8)
    - Quinault Indian Tribe (Supplementary Material) (Reel 22, Frame 40)
    - Ra-Ri (Reel 22, Frame 80)
    - Rocky Mountain Center on Environment (Reel 22, Frame 196)
    - Ro (Reel 22, Frame 477)
    - Ru (Reel 22, Frame 581)
    - Salk Institute for Biological Studies (C-R) (Reel 22, Frame 614)
    - Sa (Reel 22, Frame 733)
    - Schwartz, Herman (Reel 22, Frame 923)
    - Sc (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Se-Sh (Reel 23, Frame 276)
    - Society for Health and Human Values (Reel 23, Frame 362)
    - Southern (I-U) (Reel 23, Frame 469)
    - Southwest Creative Film Center (Reel 23, Frame 749)
    - Si-So (Reel 23, Frame 842)
    - Sp (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Stanford University (A-P) (Reel 24, Frame 116)
    - State University (C-N) (Reel 24, Frame 260)
    - Syracuse University (Regional Learning Service) (Reel 24, Frame 573)
    - St-Sy (Reel 24, Frame 683)
    - Texas Agricultural and Mechanical University (A-R) (Reel 24, Frame 861)
    - T-Te (Reel 24, Frame 1038)
    - Th-Tw (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (A-T) (Reel 25, Frame 179)
    - United States, Agriculture (Kriesberg, Martin) (Reel 25, Frame 459)
    - United States, Agriculture (A-W) (Reel 25, Frame 496)
    - United States (C-N) (Reel 25, Frame 595)
    - United States (P-T) (Reel 25, Frame 747)
    - United States News and World Report (Reel 25, Frame 927)
    - United States Theatre Centre (Reel 25, Frame 931)
    - United (B-S) (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - University of California (Environmental Studies Program, Santa Cruz) (Reel 26, Frame 104)
    - University of California (A-F) (Reel 26, Frame 260)
    - University of California (Gorney, Roderic) (Reel 26, Frame 421)
    - University of California (H-L) (Reel 26, Frame 557)
    - University of California (Nitrogen Fixation) (Reel 26, Frame 737)
    - University of California (M-Y) (Reel 26, Frame 860)
    - University of Chicago (B-S) (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - University (A-D) (Reel 27, Frame 235)
    - University of Florida (L-S) (Reel 27, Frame 400)
    - University of Illinois (A-T) (Reel 27, Frame 592)
    - University (G-I) (Reel 27, Frame 985)
    - University of Michigan (B-P) (Reel 27, Frame 1116)
    - University of Minnesota (B-W) (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - University (K-M) (Reel 28, Frame 45)
    - University of North Carolina (B-U) (Reel 28, Frame 360)
    - University (N) (Reel 28, Frame 564)
    - University (P-S) (Reel 28, Frame 791)
    - University of Wisconsin (A-U) (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - University (T-W) (Reel 29, Frame 238)
    - U (Reel 29, Frame 380)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc. (Reel 29, Frame 405)
    - V (Reel 29, Frame 463)
    - Wa (Reel 29, Frame 628)
    - We (Reel 29, Frame 782)
    - Wiarda, Howard J. (Reel 29, Frame 996)
    - Wichita (Education) (Reel 29, Frame 1061)
    - Wilson, Woodrow Foundation (N-R) (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - Wisconsin Balanced Growth and Development Council (Reel 30, Frame 180)
    - Wh-Wi (Reel 30, Frame 301)
    - Women's History Research Center, Inc. (Reel 30, Frame 450)
    - Wo-Wu (Reel 30, Frame 519)
    - Yale University (C-S) (Reel 30, Frame 695)
    - Y-Z (Reel 30, Frame 865)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1972/200.A
      - A-J (Reel 30, Frame 946)
      - University of California (Medical School) (Reel 30, Frame 1040)
      - Yeshiva University (H-M) (Reel 30, Frame 1043)
      - M-Y (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - United States - Nursing, 1972/200.C
      - Yale University (School of Nursing) (Reel 31, Frame 135)
    - United States - Fellowships, 1972/200.E
      - L-W (Reel 31, Frame 144)
    - United States - Declinations, 1972/200.F
      - A-U (Reel 31, Frame 243)
      - L-T (Reel 31, Frame 357)
    - United States - Declinations Outside Program, 1972/200.FO
      - L-T (Reel 31, Frame 357)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1972/200.S
      - University of Wisconsin (Reel 31, Frame 408)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, 1972/200.W
      - Johns Hopkins University (Snail Study) (Reel 31, Frame 435)
  - Philippines, 1972/242
    - A-P (Reel 31, Frame 438)
    - R-U (Reel 31, Frame 630)
    - Philippines - Nursing, 1972/242.C
      - University of the Philippines (Nursing School) (Reel 31, Frame 831)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/242.D
      - R-U (Reel 31, Frame 834)
  - Puerto Rico, 1972/243
    - P-T (Reel 31, Frame 848)
  - Virgin Islands, 1972/257
    - C-E (Reel 31, Frame 855)
  - Internship Program - Minority School Superintendents, 1972/260
    - Candidates (A-W) (Reel 31, Frame 878)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1972/272
    - B-W (Reel 31, Frame 989)
    - Playwrights in Residence - Declinations, 1972/272.F
      - W-Z (Reel 31, Frame 1022)
  - South America and Latin America, 1972/300
    - I (Reel 31, Frame 1028)
    - L-P (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - South America and Latin America - Medical Sciences, 1972/300.A
      - Pan American (C-F) (Reel 32, Frame 65)
  - Argentina, 1972/301
    - G-R (Reel 32, Frame 174)
  - Brazil, 1972/305
    - B-U (Reel 32, Frame 221)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1972/305.A
      - University of Bahia (Medical School) (Reel 32, Frame 470)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/305.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 32, Frame 474)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1972/305.E
      - B-S (Reel 32, Frame 493)
  - Chile, 1972/309
    - A-U (Reel 32, Frame 535)
    - Chile - Declinations Outside Program, 1972/309.FO
      - Parada, Jorge (Reel 32, Frame 573)
  - Colombia, 1972/311
    - A-U (Reel 32, Frame 579)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1972/311.A
      - University of Antioquia (Medical School) (Reel 32, Frame 831)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/311.D
      - A-C (Reel 32, Frame 834)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, 1972/311.E
      - 311E (Reel 32, Frame 909)
      - A-Z (Reel 32, Frame 921)
  - Costa Rica, 1972/313
    - Morales, Jose Carlos (Reel 32, Frame 1126)
  - Ecuador, 1972/317
    - Teran B., Gabriel (Reel 32, Frame 1132)
  - Guatemala, 1972/319
    - M-S (Reel 32, Frame 1135)
    - Guatemala - Fellowships, 1972/319.E
      - Paiz A., Oscar Humberto (Reel 32, Frame 1147)
  - Haiti, 1972/320
    - Christian Social Works Committee (Reel 32, Frame 1149)
  - Honduras, 1972/321
    - Viscovich R., Ivan (Reel 32, Frame 1154)
  - Mexico, 1972/323
    - A-U (Reel 32, Frame 1157)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1972/323.A
      - G-U (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, 1972/323.E
      - 323E (Reel 33, Frame 8)
      - A-V (Reel 33, Frame 10)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1972/323.R
      - 323R (Reel 33, Frame 279)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1972/323.S
      - 323S (Reel 33, Frame 281)
  - Nicaragua, 1972/325
    - National Committee on Economic Reconstruction (Reel 33, Frame 295)
    - Nicaragua - Fellowships, 1972/325.E
      - E-S (Reel 33, Frame 325)
  - Paraguay, 1972/329
    - B-O (Reel 33, Frame 330)
    - Gonzalez, Enrique (Reel 33, Frame 338)
    - Paraguay - Fellowships, 1972/329.E
      - Gonzalez, Enrique (Reel 33, Frame 338)
  - Peru, 1972/331
    - A-W (Reel 33, Frame 340)
    - Peru - Fellowships, 1972/331.E
      - G-V (Reel 33, Frame 488)
  - El Salvador, 1972/333
    - D-Z (Reel 33, Frame 494)
    - El Salvador - Fellowships, 1972/333.E
      - H-S (Reel 33, Frame 521)
  - Uruguay, 1972/337
    - Trenchi, Hebert (Reel 33, Frame 532)
  - Venezuela, 1972/339
    - M-N (Reel 33, Frame 537)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/339.D
      - Agriculture (Rodriguez Viso, Miguel) (Reel 33, Frame 546)
  - Great Britain, 1972/400
    - Commonwealth Development Corporation (Swynnerton, Roger J. M.) (Reel 33, Frame 548)
  - England, 1972/401
    - A-I (Reel 33, Frame 558)
    - L-T (Reel 33, Frame 660)
    - University of Liverpool (Zaria Proposal) (Reel 33, Frame 743)
    - U-Y (Reel 33, Frame 986)
  - Ireland, 1972/403
    - A-R (Reel 34, Frame 1)
  - Scotland, 1972/405
    - University of Edinburgh (Centre for Reproductive Biology) (Reel 34, Frame 11)
    - L-U (Reel 34, Frame 138)
  - Wales, 1972/407
    - University College, Cardiff (Population) (Reel 34, Frame 162)
  - Australia, 1972/410
    - A-U (Reel 34, Frame 167)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1972/410.A
      - University of New South Wales (Reel 34, Frame 278)
  - New Zealand, 1972/418
    - A-V (Reel 34, Frame 286)
    - New Zealand - Virus Studies, 1972/418.V
      - University of Otago (Reel 34, Frame 322)
  - Fiji, 1972/419
    - University of the South Pacific (Reel 34, Frame 325)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1972/420
    - Medical Research in the British Caribbean (Reel 34, Frame 328)
    - Caribbean Region and Central America - Medical Sciences, 1972/420.A
      - Caribbean Committee for Bilharzia Research (Reel 34, Frame 333)
  - Canada, 1972/427
    - A-H (Reel 34, Frame 390)
    - International Development Research Center (H-R) (Reel 34, Frame 445)
    - M-S (Reel 34, Frame 573)
    - University (B-W) (Reel 34, Frame 734)
    - York University (Merrens, H. Roy) (Reel 34, Frame 912)
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/427.D
      - Agriculture (H-M) (Reel 34, Frame 923)
  - Bermuda, 1972/430
    - Bermuda Biological Station for Research (Seawater System) (Reel 34, Frame 928)
  - Barbados, 1972/435
    - Caribbean Development Bank (Ayre-Smith, R. A.) (Reel 34, Frame 950)
  - Jamaica, 1972/437
    - University of the West Indies (H-W) (Reel 34, Frame 953)
  - Leeward Islands, 1972/439
    - Dannenborg Farms (Granger, James M. M.) (Reel 34, Frame 1007)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1972/451
    - University of the West Indies (I-T) (Reel 34, Frame 1009)
  - Windward Islands, 1972/455
    - C-S (Reel 34, Frame 1039)
    - Windward Islands - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/455.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 34, Frame 1061)
  - Sri Lanka, 1972/462
    - D-U (Reel 34, Frame 1085)
    - Sri Lanka - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/462.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 34, Frame 1100)
    - Sri Lanka - Fellowships, 1972/462.E
      - 462E (Reel 34, Frame 1102)
      - Jayawardena, G. (Reel 34, Frame 1107)
  - Hong Kong, 1972/463
    - C-W (Reel 34, Frame 1111)
  - India, 1972/464
    - A-X (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University, Farm Economics (Supplementary Material) (Reel 35, Frame 181)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1972/464.A
      - A-V (Reel 35, Frame 363)
    - India - Fellowships, 1972/464.E
      - B-S (Reel 35, Frame 377)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1972/464.S
      - Social Sciences (Reel 35, Frame 420)
  - Pakistan, 1972/465
    - A-S (Reel 35, Frame 426)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1972/472
    - Wau Ecology Institute (Reel 35, Frame 454)
  - Malaysia, 1972/473
    - H-S (Reel 35, Frame 465)
    - Malaysia - Fellowships, 1972/473.E
      - Omar, Othman bin (Reel 35, Frame 492)
  - Nepal, 1972/474
    - A-C (Reel 35, Frame 497)
  - Africa, 1972/475
    - A-C (Reel 35, Frame 575)
    - Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/475.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 35, Frame 684)
  - Kenya, 1972/476
    - A-U (Reel 35, Frame 695)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, 1972/476.E
      - C-W (Reel 35, Frame 887)
  - East Africa Region, 1972/477
    - E-F (Reel 35, Frame 944)
  - Rhodesia, 1972/483
    - P-U (Reel 35, Frame 1009)
  - Republic of South Africa, 1972/489
    - Neitz, Wilhelm O. (Reel 35, Frame 1016)
  - Uganda, 1972/492
    - D-V (Reel 35, Frame 1053)
    - Uganda - Medical Sciences, 1972/492.A
      - Makerere University (Medical School) (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - Uganda - Fellowships, 1972/492.E
      - A-R (Reel 36, Frame 6)
    - Uganda - Social Sciences, 1972/492.S
      - Makerere University (Economics) (Reel 36, Frame 70)
  - Sudan, 1972/494
    - A-U (Reel 36, Frame 81)
  - West Africa Region, 1972/495
    - Rice (Reel 36, Frame 102)
    - Rice (Supplementary Material) (Reel 36, Frame 153)
    - C-S (Reel 36, Frame 559)
    - West Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/495.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 36, Frame 564)
  - Ghana, 1972/496
    - B-U (Reel 36, Frame 567)
  - Nigeria, 1972/497
    - A-O (Reel 36, Frame 571)
    - University of Ibadan, Agricultural Business Management (B-S) (Reel 36, Frame 859)
    - University of Ibadan (A-Z) (Reel 36, Frame 988)
    - University (I-N) (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - Nigeria - Medical Sciences, 1972/497.A
      - A-U (Reel 37, Frame 199)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/497.D
      - University of Ibadan (Land Tenure Seminar) (Reel 37, Frame 280)
      - University of Nigeria (Agriculture) (Reel 37, Frame 519)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, 1972/497.E
      - A-Z (Reel 37, Frame 523)
    - Nigeria - Social Sciences, 1972/497.S
      - University of Ibadan (E-S) (Reel 37, Frame 619)
  - Sierra Leone, 1972/499
    - R-U (Reel 37, Frame 636)
  - France, 1972/500
    - I-U (Reel 37, Frame 649)
  - Ivory Coast, 1972/527
    - Institute of Research for Oils and Oil Seeds (Oil Palm) (Reel 37, Frame 887)
  - Senegal, 1972/531
    - P-T (Reel 37, Frame 900)
  - Asia and Far East Asia, 1972/600
    - Directors of Research and Training Institutes in Asia (Reel 37, Frame 916)
    - Asia and Far East Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/600.D
      - G-W (Reel 37, Frame 956)
  - Taiwan, 1972/605
    - Asian Vegetable Development Center (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction (L-T) (Reel 38, Frame 282)
    - Taiwan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/605.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 38, Frame 299)
  - Japan, 1972/609
    - Keio University (Library School) (Reel 38, Frame 309)
    - F-Y (Reel 38, Frame 434)
  - Korea, 1972/613
    - E-K (Reel 38, Frame 517)
  - Thailand, 1972/617
    - A-U (Reel 38, Frame 527)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1972/617.A
      - Ramathibodi Faculty of Medicine (Reel 38, Frame 634)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1972/617.E
      - 617E (Reel 38, Frame 642)
      - A-W (Reel 38, Frame 644)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1972/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics) (Reel 38, Frame 751)
  - Southeast Asia Region, 1972/625
    - Southeast Asian Ministers of Education Secretariat (Reel 38, Frame 1043)
  - Holland, 1972/650
    - B-U (Reel 38, Frame 1047)
  - Indonesia, 1972/652
    - G-U (Reel 38, Frame 1057)
    - Indonesia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/652.D
      - Agriculture (Corn Improvement) (Reel 39, Frame 1)
  - Ethiopia, 1972/701
    - H-Y (Reel 39, Frame 5)
    - Ethiopia - Fellowships, 1972/701.E
      - D-W (Reel 39, Frame 27)
  - Afghanistan, 1972/703
    - Ghafoor, Abdul (Reel 39, Frame 57)
    - Afghanistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1972/703.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 39, Frame 60)
  - Austria, 1972/705
    - Ekhart, Walter (Reel 39, Frame 76)
  - Belgium, 1972/707
    - Inter-University Committee for Agronomic Research (Reel 39, Frame 79)
    - Belgium - Nursing, 1972/707.C
      - University of Brussels (Reel 39, Frame 87)
  - Zaire, 1972/709
    - B-N (Reel 39, Frame 92)
    - Zaire - Medical Sciences, 1972/709.A
      - National University of Zaire (Medical School) (Reel 39, Frame 113)
    - Zaire - Fellowships, 1972/709.E
      - D-T (Reel 39, Frame 120)
  - Yugoslavia, 1972/710
    - University of Ljubljana (Family Planning Institute) (Reel 39, Frame 144)
  - Denmark, 1972/713
    - D-H (Reel 39, Frame 147)
  - Germany, 1972/717
    - B-V (Reel 39, Frame 158)
  - Tanzania, 1972/723
    - S-U (Reel 39, Frame 208)
    - Tanzania - Medical Sciences, 1972/723.A
      - University of Dar es Salaam (Medical School) (Reel 39, Frame 249)
    - Tanzania - Fellowships, 1972/723.E